Let's go inside the restaurant!
Ahhh, I'm eating a Thai grill!
Oh, that's good!
Yesterday was so good!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
LOL!
How is it?
Mmmm...
Let's go inside!
Let's go inside the store!
Take a video!
Okay!
Lunch at the same time!
Cheers!
Cheers.
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Oh, here comes YouTube! It's real!
Hello!
You're on YouTube?
YouTuber?
I'm a YouTuber!
Anpanman!
What kind of YouTuber are you?
You want to turn it off?
Cut it out once!
Congratulations!
Let me see!
Have you eaten too much?
No, thank you! Not today!
Three shrimp!
I haven't finished yet!
I have to finish!
Not today!
Sushi and red cabbage sushi!
It's a greedy set!
Delicious!
I'm full!
Sit down!
Sit down! Sit back!
Force the little girls to sit down!
I have something I want you all to see!
Today's MC!
Watch!
She's so great!
Rina Matsu!
That's all she said today!
Rina Matsu is really great!
You know?
I don't want you to say that!
I just want you to see her!
I really respect you!
I'm not doing it on purpose!
I really want to tell you!
You guys are so kind.
That's what they say!
Take it off him!
Sorry! My turn is over!
It's delicious!
It's so good!
Yummy?
I got a lot of them.
I got a lot of it.
What's that?
I don't know.
It's delicious.
Oh, my God.
It's good.
Okonomiyaki.
Delicious!
Akimoto
Okonomiyaki
Bon appétit!
Oh, you don't do it!
Is it a picture, not a video?
It's a video.
But it wasn't quite right.
Thank you very much.
Here's where we're going.
Salmon side.
Samosama.
Azuki beans.
He's cute.
What did you do?
Mifultai and hamo.
What? What was that?
Muffed Tortie and Hamo.
Adult.
Not much seafood sushi.
Certainly not.
Only reasonably priced seafood sushi.Only reasonably priced seafood sushi.
Because I've never been there.
I'll eat what I can't eat.
I'm going to eat.
I'm having the taiyaki.
That's good.
It's started.
No hunchback.
Look at me.
You're so cute.
Really hunched over.
Salmon and...
Toro and...
Negitoro?
They're the same.
He's so cute.
Look at that.
So cute!
Yes, it is.
Oh, I like it.
Cute.
Ha!
Too close!
Souvenirs.
A square.
Okonomiyaki.
No, not okonomiyaki!
We're eating okonomiyaki.
The back is blurred.
That's right.
A square!
I've already eaten all of them!
I ate all of them!
I like sushi.
Oh, no.
Sushi
I also got a souvenir!
Sushi from Saka Egis!
I would like to try the tuna first!
Inonmai, it's an eating book!
Then I'll have it again, please.
That's inori!
Uma
It's a little, um, like acting.
LOL!
It smells like an act.
Okay, what do you think? Was it good?
It's like you were alive just now.
You didn't.
You're not alive.
I really wanted to try this pudding.
I found it in the fridge a while ago.
I thought it was probably someone else's, so I gave up on it.
I'm eating it.
I'm so sleepy.
So sleepy. So sleepy.
I'm so sleepy. The show's over.
I'm so sleepy, I want to go to bed right now, but look...
I have to wash in the bath
Yes, it's hard work, I have to take this off
Let's go to bed, let's go to bed
I went to bed.
He said all the ones I recommended.
Looks delicious
Bon appétit!
The green onions are delicious.
Here you go. May I?
You sure are. You look really good.
You're not fine?
Why not?
Every single one of you is fine.
Come on, guys, try it.
I see you and Mr. Banana came to see me over here.
I said hello to him.
He was so excited to see you.
After hearing that.
I wanted him to see more live performances.
I've been trying to have him put that kind of thought into it.
And the people who see the show...
I was so grateful and happy to hear that everyone said it was so good.
I'm really grateful and happy.
So I want to do more live shows so that people can see us live more.
I want to do it.
I'm sure we'll do it.
Bye bye!
Have a safe trip home!
Bye-bye.
Take care.
Bye-bye birthday.
Bye-bye birdie.
Lena's bathroom.
You can push her head in.
I'm not leaving.
The tour is over.
Thank you very much.
Hey, bro.
Oh, hey.Oh?
How's it smell?
Do I smell good? Hey, bro.
I love your smell, Arin.
How was it? It was good.
He's been really into udon lately.
She loved it.
It was delicious.
Let's have dessert and go home.
Thank you very much.
Watch the next video!